<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tutorial Compose</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="label_author">Penerbit: %s</string>
    <string name="free_sample">Free Sample</string>
    <string name="name_dicoding">Renaldy Sabdo Jati Purboningrat</string>
    <string name="email_dicoding">renalraion@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="title_book_1">The Personal MBA</string>
    <string name="author_book_1">Renaldy Team</string>
    <string name="desc_book_1">The consensus is clear: MBA programs are a waste of time and money. Even the elite schools offer outdated assembly-line educations about profit-and-loss statements and PowerPoint presentations. After two years poring over sanitized case studies, students are shuffled off into middle management to find out how business really works.</string>
    <string name="title_book_2">Zero To One</string>
    <string name="author_book_2">Sabdo Jati</string>
    <string name="desc_book_2"><![CDATA[<The great secret of our time is that there are still uncharted frontiers to explore and new inventions to create. In Zero to One, legendary entrepreneur and investor Peter Thiel shows how we can find singular ways to create those new things.<br>
Thiel begins with the contrarian premise that we live in an age of technological stagnation, even if we’re too distracted by shiny mobile devices to notice. Information technology has improved rapidly, but there is no reason why progress should be limited to computers or Silicon Valley. Progress can be achieved in any industry or area of business. It comes from the most important skill that every leader must master: learning to think for yourself.]]></string>
    <string name="title_book_3">The Power of Subconscious Mind</string>
    <string name="author_book_3">Steven Wongso</string>
    <string name="desc_book_3">Change your life by changing your beliefs! This users guide to the mind explains how to control the force of subconscious thought with the techniques of autosuggestion and visualization. Learn how to attain self-confidence, create harmonious relationships, accumulate wealth, overcome fears, banish bad habits, promote physical healing, and achieve well-being and happiness. Dr. Murphys techniques have helped readers all over the world. Inspiring examples throughout this book attest to the effectiveness of his methods.</string>
    <string name="title_book_4">How to Fail At Most Everything and Still Win Big</string>
    <string name="author_book_4">Dicky Kuncoro</string>
    <string name="desc_book_4">Scott Adams has likely failed at more things than anyone you have ever met or anyone you have even heard of. So how did he go from hapless office worker and serial failure to the creator of Dilbert, one of the world’s most famous syndicated comic strips, in just a few years? In How to Fail at Almost Everything and Still Win Big, Adams shares the game plan he’s followed since he was a teen: invite failure in, embrace it, then pick its pocket.</string>
    <string name="title_book_5">The Truth About Wuhan</string>
    <string name="author_book_5">Riska R.S</string>
    <string name="desc_book_5">The day that Dr. Andrew G. Huff left his senior scientist and vice president role at EcoHealth Alliance was one of the happiest days of his life due to the corruption he had witnessed at the organization. However, he never thought working there would be of any great consequence to the future. He was wrong. Because, as an EcoHealth Alliance insider, Dr. Huff had had a ringside seat to one of the biggest cover-ups in history. </string>
    <string name="title_book_6">The Art Of Public Speaking</string>
    <string name="author_book_6">Fadli Dadil</string>
    <string name="desc_book_6">Whether you want to improve your performance in sales, leadership, interpersonal skills, communications, presentations or customer service, youll find a resource here that perfectly work for you. Youll have a skill that will help power your performance and your career to the next level an experience that has already helped million people become major successes in all walks of life.</string>
    <string name="title_book_7">Revisi Takdir</string>
    <string name="author_book_7">Nurul Fikriyah</string>
    <string name="desc_book_7"><![CDATA[<Banyak dari kita yang memiliki mispersepsi pada takdir. Menganggap bahwa segala hal yang terjadi dalam hidup ini sudah digaristangankan, sampai terlalu enggan untuk berusaha mengubah banyak hal karena beranggapan bahwa sudah takdir.
Padahal tidak semua takdir itu bersifat mutlak, loh. Dalam beberapa hal, takdir masihlah di persimpangan, hingga tujuan yang akan kita dapatkan bergantung dengan jalan mana yang akan kita pilih.]]></string>
    <string name="title_book_8">Jangan Membuat Masalah Kecil Jadi Masalah Besar</string>
    <string name="author_book_8">Kharis S.kom M kom</string>
    <string name="desc_book_8">Banyak hal dalam hidup ini yang sebenarnya hanya masalah kecil, tapi kita memperlakukannya sebagai masalah besar. Sebenarnya, dengan membentuk perspektif baru bahwa masalah-masalah itu memang kecil, kita akan mempunyai lebih banyak waktu untuk memikirkan hal-hal yang benar-benar merupakan masalah besar. Dengan gaya tulisan yang mudah dipahami, buku ini menyajikan cara-cara membentuk perspektif yang lebih positif tersebut sehingga kita akan belajar untuk berdamai dengan diri sendiri dan lebih peduli. Hidup kita akan lebih terfokus pada masa kini, hubungan kita dengan orang lain akan menjadi lebih baik, dan batin kita akan menjadi lebih tenang.</string>
    <string name="title_book_9">Detektif Conan</string>
    <string name="author_book_9">Kakanda Anang</string>
    <string name="desc_book_9">This carefully crafted ebook: "The Complete Sherlock Holmes Other Crime Mysteries" is formatted for your eReader with a functional and detailed table of contents: Sherlock Holmes Mysteries A Study in Scarlet The Sign of Four The Hound of the Baskervilles The Valley of Fear The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes The Memoirs of Sherlock Holmes The Return of Sherlock Holmes His Last Bow The Case Book of Sherlock Holmes The Field Bazaar How Watson Learned the Trick Other Mysteries Mystery of Cloomber The Firm of Girdlestone Mysteries and Adventures The Gully of Bluemansdyke</string>
    <string name="title_book_10">ReDefine Yourself</string>
    <string name="author_book_10">Project A Team</string>
    <string name="desc_book_10">Those who said that people can’t change didnt know this book. People can change but they wont if they choose not to.
In this book you have a chance to change yourself, not others. And by doing this, you will realize how your emotions affect people around you and your wealth as well.</string>
</resources>